Woke up this morning, the world was gray Didn't
know the colors had all faded away Been living in
a room with the curtains drawn tight Then you
flipped a switch and turned on the light I'm
seeing an electric color Finding a rhythm I
never knew Dancing in a brand new summer My whole
world feels bright and new It's an electric
color feeling And it all started with you
The city sounds were just a buzz in my ear A static
station I could never quite hear But now the
noise is turning into a song And I finally feel
like I belong I'm seeing an electric color
Finding a rhythm I never knew Dancing in a brand
new summer My whole world feels bright anew It's
an electric color feeling And it all started
with you
The beat is getting stronger I can't hide it any
longer My heart is playing catch up to the music
Turning way
up
I'm seeing an electric color Finding a rhythm I
never knew Dancing in a brand new summer My whole
world feels bright anew It's an electric color
feeling And it all started with you. Electric
color, feeling so new. It's all because of you.